(Full Stack Developer)

Background

5+ years of Development/Maintenance/Support experience UI Development and Backend Services. Presenty working as a software engineer in Cisco . Previously, programmer at Amazecodes solutions.

Technology Skills

AngularJS (1.X)	AngularJS (2.X)	JavaScript	jQuery	Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)	HTML
Bootstrap Php	Laravel Mys	ql .Net C#	Python Django		

Version Control



Experience

Cisco (Software Engineer)

September 2016 - Present

Client: AT&T

- Involved in developing the application and make it a angular module, Front End
 Design and Development using Angular js, design html.
- Code verification and Merge the codes for deployment and request deployment to deployment Team.
- Find a common functional module and make it as a Directive for reducing duplicate code.

Client : Rogers

- Involved in developing the application and make it a angular module, Front End Design and Development using Angular js, design html.
- · Involved in JIRA, Content bug fix.

Amazecodes Solution (Software Engineer)

May 2014 - August 2016

QuoteFreeze

- Involved in developing the application using the MVC Architecture.
- Involved in writing the business logic for various modules in the application.
- Involved in requirement analysis and Design & development from scratch
- Front End Development using Angular js and C# , Back End Development using SQL Server
- Handling a team of UI developers

DirectVerify.me

- Understanding the storyboard based on that designing process will carry out by using html and jquery.
- UI development and maintenance.
- Web API Development.
- · Involved in JIRA bug fix raised by QA.

Zorse Labs (Python, Django developer)

May 2013 - April 2014

Shiksha

- · Involved in developing the application using the python django framework.
- · Involved in writing the business logic for various modules in the application.
- Involved in requirement analysis and Design & development from scratch

Get in touch

■ fahadph777@gmail.com

9620214213

Education

B.S.C (Computer science)

GNIIT from NIIT

MCA (Currently Doing)

Core qualities

Adaptive, Quick learner, Team player, Team builder.

Awards

Won the Pat On The Back Awards Broadsoft 2017.

Won the Pat On The Back Awards Amazecodes solutions 2016.

Interests

Trekking and Travelling

• Front End Development using Angular js , Back End Development using

PostgresSQL